Guide to the Gravity Probe B records SC1274
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Public Relations
  - Walter Cruttenden, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - George Merlis - media consulting, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Media training, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - GP-B Magazine Articles, 2005, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - NASA GP-B PAO Plan, 2003 Jul (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - S- docs P- docs lists, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Pre-launch Daily Mission Status Reports, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - GP-B spinoffs - from Einstein to Farming, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Torque Rods, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Telescope Drawings, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Polhode Story, 2006 Nov 16 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper articles, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - NY Times Science/ Gravity articles, 2005-2007 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - News stories Space, Cosmology, Astronomy, 2003, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - APS Matters of Gravity Newsletter, 2005 Fall (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - GP-B Critique Comments, 2004 Apr, Jul (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Einstein Doubters, 2004 May-Jun (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Web/ online articles, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Nature Article, 2006 Dec (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Frame- dragging experiments, 2006 Nov, 2007 Jan (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Ciafolini Paulis Article coverage, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - other GR Experiments, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Popular science award, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - GP-B bibliography - scientific technical, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Relativity Gravity book info, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Everitt - Countdown to launch, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Calden Jones GP-B Management, 2006 Apr, May (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - GP-B case study - GW University, 2007 Fall (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - GP-B scientific technical papers, undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - GP-B Risk Analysis, 2005 Jan 5 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - GP-B Scientific/ Engineering papers, 2004 Sep (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Ben Lange - dissertation, 1964 Jun (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Articles about Science, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Wikipedia - spacetime relativity, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Misc. article on physics, Einstein, Relativity, etc, undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - McGraw Hill article, 2008 Feb (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - empty folders, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - GP-B Identity items, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Clothing - Land's End other, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Srudio reflex, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - GP-B print, patches, stickers, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Gravity Probe B Project - studio reflex, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - PAO Products studio reflex, 2002 Nov 25 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - GP-B PAO products, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Relativity and determinism, 2003, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Scientific American magazine, 1999 Jan (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - GP-B PA+ EPO Product Matrix, 2003, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Old EPO materials, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - museum exhibits, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Einstein exhibit - skinball, 2004 Jun (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - inquiries to be answered, 2004-2005 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 15th edition superconductivity, 2008 May 16 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Hand-written inquiries, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Pocket epitome meeting, 2007 Apr 14-17 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Lockheed Martin folder, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - GP-B public affairs plan, 2003 Jul (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Robert A. Kahn proposal, 2003 Mar 14 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2005 May 11 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2005 Oct 12 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2005 Dec 7 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2005 Apr 5 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Report newspaper, 2007 Apr 18 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Marshal Star NASA, 2005 Oct 13 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Newsline, 2005 Jun 3 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Design News, 2005 Apr 18 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - inView, 2005 Dec (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Natural History magazine, 2005 Mar (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Astronomy Magazine, 2008 Jan (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Los Angeles Times newspaper, 2004 Feb 24 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - The Boston Globe newspaper, 2004 Apr 3 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Educational outreach plan, 2004-2007 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - E PO Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - The Peninsula newspaper, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 2005 Apr 5 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - San Jose Mercury News, 2004 Apr 13 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - international newspaper, undated (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Gravity Probe B Delta Program, undated (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Bulletin of the American Physical Society, 2007 Apr 14-17 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - VRC - Search Retrieval Project, 2003 Dec 23 (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - Ask Magazine Living with the Contractor, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Launch timeline Architecture, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Feedback questionaire, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Gravity Earth's oblateness, 2005 Mar (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Abernation of Starlight- Technical, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Abernation of Starlight - history use, 2005 Jul (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - GP-B data reduction, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Gee Whiz" quick facts, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - GP-B in a nutshell, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Gravity Probe B NASA facts, 2005 Jan (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Gravity Probe B Fact Sheet, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - New Fact Sheets, 2005 Feb (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Gravity Probe B info sheet, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Press kit NASA GP-B experiment, 2004 Apr (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Natural History magazine, 2005 Mar (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Sky and Telescope magazine, 2005 Jul (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - New Scientist magazine, 2005 Apr 2 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Discover magazine, 2004 Sep (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - popular science magazine, 2004 Dec (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Discover presents Einstein magazine, 2009 Spring (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Space Research Today magazine, 2007 Dec (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Marshall Star, 2005 Oct 13 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Astronomy Magazine special issue, 2008 Jan (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - The New York Times - Science Times, 2004 Apr 13 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Report, 2006 Apr 5 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Stanford Report, 2005 May 11 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Report, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Report, 2005 Oct 12 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Report, 2005 Oct 12 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Stanford Report, 2006 Apr 5 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Report, 2005 May 11 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Stanford Report, 2007 Apr 18 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Report, 2005 Oct 12 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Stanford Report, 2007 Apr 18 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Gravity Probe B information folders, undated (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Invoices, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Gravity, undated (Box 29, Folder 42)